<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<GPP><H><SMR>GPC Scripts</SMR><TOT>3472</TOT><CPG>1</CPG><TPG>193</TPG><RES>Results: 19 ~ 37 of 3472</RES></H><S><SID>12408</SID><UID>619203</UID><NAM>MODERN WARFARE 447</NAM><DES>This might actually

be the 

WORST DESCRIPTION OF ALL TIME.

</DES><RTP>8</RTP><RTM>4</RTM><UTM>1663449314</UTM><DOW>566</DOW><NOT>First one</NOT><VER>1.00</VER><UNM>ImMexicanOng</UNM><TID>0</TID></S><S><SID>12407</SID><UID>365955</UID><NAM>Mw2 beta</NAM><DES>test script for beta

obeattzy#9867</DES><RTP>51</RTP><RTM>34</RTM><UTM>1663414401</UTM><DOW>4489</DOW><NOT>test for mw2</NOT><VER>1.00</VER><UNM>beattzy332</UNM><TID>0</TID></S><S><SID>12406</SID><UID>497702</UID><NAM>NHL 22</NAM><DES>NHL XX Script
note: its meant for NHL 22, but it should work on any NHL</DES><RTP>0</RTP><RTM>2</RTM><UTM>1663257367</UTM><DOW>266</DOW><NOT>F   E   A   T   U   R   E   S
===============NHL=================
	  HOW TO ACTIVATE DEKES
___________________________________
L3 + CROSS 		= TAP BACK
===================================
L3 + SQUARE 	= BETWEEN THE LEGS not workin (one touch deke)
===================================
L3 + TRIANGLE 	= ONE HAND TUCK
===================================
L3 + CIRCLE 	= ZETTERBERG
___________________________________
- VM RUNNING AT ( 3 ms ).</NOT><VER>3</VER><UNM>noctwrnyA</UNM><TID>0</TID></S><S><SID>12390</SID><UID>412485</UID><NAM>Division 2 Combo Script AFK Tombs</NAM><DES>Please Read the Instructions on How To Use !
Added New Feathers And Mods  Now  With Hair Triggers !
Enjoy 😎</DES><RTP>4</RTP><RTM>7</RTM><UTM>1662950948</UTM><DOW>465</DOW><NOT>Please Read the Instructions on How To Use !
Added New Feathers And Mods  Now  With Hair Triggers !
Enjoy 😎</NOT><VER>15.3</VER><UNM>Batmanbeyond71</UNM><TID>0</TID></S><S><SID>12402</SID><UID>302557</UID><NAM>Crescens` COD MYE: Melt your enemy!  #1 for COD!</NAM><DES>Anti Recoil Extreme Precision now with ultra-fast calibration mode!
With the best Aim Assist for COD.  A GPC Power Script by Crescens.
https://bit.ly/codmye</DES><RTP>97</RTP><RTM>81</RTM><UTM>1662801570</UTM><DOW>11175</DOW><NOT>Anti Recoil Extreme Precision now with ultra-fast calibration mode!
With the best Aim Assist for COD.  A GPC Power Script by Crescens.
https://bit.ly/codmye</NOT><VER>7.5</VER><UNM>Crescens</UNM><TID>0</TID></S><S><SID>11089</SID><UID>326876</UID><NAM>The Division 2 PRO SCRIPT - ZEN ONLY</NAM><DES>Read the script for instructions on how to use it</DES><RTP>12</RTP><RTM>6</RTM><UTM>1662696064</UTM><DOW>1114</DOW><NOT>New strafe added
New mod added</NOT><VER>5.3</VER><UNM>noozbar</UNM><TID>0</TID></S><S><SID>12398</SID><UID>326876</UID><NAM>Destiny 2 - PRO</NAM><DES>Open the script in the ZEN Studio Compiler and read instructions inside the script</DES><RTP>13</RTP><RTM>12</RTM><UTM>1662695925</UTM><DOW>1439</DOW><NOT>Release</NOT><VER>1.0</VER><UNM>noozbar</UNM><TID>0</TID></S><S><SID>12394</SID><UID>666553</UID><NAM>ERSECCO SCAM</NAM><DES>ANTIRECOIL GENERALE PER TUTTI I GIOCHI!</DES><RTP>6</RTP><RTM>2</RTM><UTM>1662541048</UTM><DOW>507</DOW><NOT>Prossima versione con Aim Assist, Rapid Fire!</NOT><VER>1.0</VER><UNM>Twin</UNM><TID>0</TID></S><S><SID>12210</SID><UID>412485</UID><NAM>batdiversion advanced version for the pros</NAM><DES>Added A lot to list Too much 
Please Read The Instructions!
More Updates to Come
Enjoy</DES><RTP>5</RTP><RTM>3</RTM><UTM>1662422550</UTM><DOW>694</DOW><NOT>not so simple  
Added A lot to list Too much 
Please Read The Instructions!
More Updates to Come
Enjoy</NOT><VER>4.0</VER><UNM>Batmanbeyond71</UNM><TID>0</TID></S><S><SID>12391</SID><UID>646582</UID><NAM>Halo: MCC - Halo 2 Classic - Combo Scripts</NAM><DES>Hello,

This script has been written and tested with Steam - Halo: MCC - Halo 2. The button layout I use is Recon, you can modify the button mapping as needed. In the future, I will write in commented button layouts so you can choose your layout.

Right now when you load this, the BXR and Doubleshot Button Combos are written. Starting the script has them turned on by default. Clicking the Right DPAD will turn off/on Doubleshot and clicking the Left DPAD will turn off/on the BXR.

I will in time write in plausible menu features, but I am making this quite simple as Halo 2 Classic is very outdated.</DES><RTP>0</RTP><RTM>1</RTM><UTM>1662218280</UTM><DOW>67</DOW><NOT>Initial Release of the script.</NOT><VER>1.00</VER><UNM>silentslay</UNM><TID>0</TID></S><S><SID>12389</SID><UID>455251</UID><NAM>YOU'RE JUST BETTER V59.2: ScottishTryHard 32_Bit V4.1</NAM><DES>YOU'RE JUST BETTER V59.2: ScottishTryHard 32_Bit V4.1 EDITION BY DOMEKILLER</DES><RTP>12</RTP><RTM>6</RTM><UTM>1661998350</UTM><DOW>2160</DOW><NOT>Credits: Crescens and Taylor compiled by scripts of many others credit goes to the cronus community.</NOT><VER>59.2</VER><UNM>DOMEKILLER</UNM><TID>0</TID></S><S><SID>12388</SID><UID>455251</UID><NAM>YOU'RE JUST BETTER V59.2: ScottishTryHard 32_Bit V4.1</NAM><DES>YOU'RE JUST BETTER V59.2: ScottishTryHard 32_Bit V4.1 EDITION BY DOMEKILLER</DES><RTP>4</RTP><RTM>4</RTM><UTM>1661997824</UTM><DOW>662</DOW><NOT>Crescens and Taylor compiled by scripts of many others credit goes to the cronus community.</NOT><VER>59.2</VER><UNM>DOMEKILLER</UNM><TID>0</TID></S><S><SID>12387</SID><UID>558993</UID><NAM>fifa 22</NAM><DES>fifa 22 Skills moves</DES><RTP>4</RTP><RTM>3</RTM><UTM>1661941436</UTM><DOW>709</DOW><NOT>hij werkt goed</NOT><VER>2.05</VER><UNM>Olaf bode</UNM><TID>0</TID></S><S><SID>12386</SID><UID>570771</UID><NAM>RUST Pedro's Nightmare 4.0   32 Bit</NAM><DES>Join the discord for help. https://discord.gg/6wvvgJU4ZM
Entire menu layout has been changed. More user friendly.
Mods were added inverted mode, auto-strafe, crouch-spam, auto code lock, you can adjust your stick sensitivity for each sight on the Zen while playing on plug and play settings.  Read ALL the instructions many things have changed.</DES><RTP>107</RTP><RTM>53</RTM><UTM>1661895674</UTM><DOW>13329</DOW><NOT>Read all the instructions.</NOT><VER>4.0</VER><UNM>Jbaze122</UNM><TID>0</TID></S><S><SID>12385</SID><UID>412485</UID><NAM>Division 2 Combo script</NAM><DES>Added AFK tombs Script 
&amp; Auto Open Cashe Script As Well</DES><RTP>5</RTP><RTM>0</RTM><UTM>1661887308</UTM><DOW>123</DOW><NOT>Took me A while to get it working right</NOT><VER>1</VER><UNM>Batmanbeyond71</UNM><TID>0</TID></S><S><SID>12384</SID><UID>313138</UID><NAM>Reactive AFK</NAM><DES>This is a reactive AFK script made for Destiny 2 but can be used in other games as long as that game has rumble feedback. Info can be found at the top of the script.</DES><RTP>2</RTP><RTM>0</RTM><UTM>1661848076</UTM><DOW>150</DOW><NOT>First released version.</NOT><VER>1.1</VER><UNM>iZapThings</UNM><TID>0</TID></S><S><SID>12383</SID><UID>412485</UID><NAM>Division 2 AFK Tombs &amp; Auto Cashe</NAM><DES>Modified Version of These 2 GPC Scripts By Zanzy123
the_division_2_efficient_medkit_cheese_1_01.gpc
The_Division_2_AFK_XP_Tombs_Mission_1_00.gpc
Modified with the ZEN Scripter Ver 10.4.1.1</DES><RTP>1</RTP><RTM>1</RTM><UTM>1661828533</UTM><DOW>93</DOW><NOT>Support The Original Author!
 Modified Version of These 2 GPC Scripts By Zanzy123
the_division_2_efficient_medkit_cheese_1_01.gpc
The_Division_2_AFK_XP_Tombs_Mission_1_00.gpc
Modified with the ZEN Scripter Ver 10.4.1.1</NOT><VER>1</VER><UNM>Batmanbeyond71</UNM><TID>0</TID></S><S><SID>12282</SID><UID>461910</UID><NAM>OneForAll  32bit 2.56</NAM><DES>/*to use the script, the latest beta of the Zen firmware and Studio version is required
                                         

OneForAll is written to have the best possible accessibility in each game, so that everyone can play games according to their needs. there are some classic mods included and many that simplify commands and movements to execute. 

if you find bugs, suggestions for improvement or would like to support me with a donation so i can buy new popular games to find possible simplifications.

for the best experince, set under menu Controller the button same as the in game buton

feel free to write me on discord username: newjack or in the official zen forum sehathabib

Thanks to Swizzy, Taylordrift and Fadexz who helped me to integrate the new storage system from Swizzy.


The script includes some special accessibility features and all the classic ones. AimAssist, SlideCancel, Switchstick, Loot Run, AutoRun, Remap, auto Cam adjustment, Doubltap mods, dpad to stick, stick switch. invert stickt, easy double jump, reload mods, R2 L2 Mods and easyhold BTN.
—————————————————————————————————————————————————————————————

New are, in Mods
—————————————————————————————————————————————————————————————

switschstick swaps the left and right stick, can be set so that it is on ly swapped when aiming. e.g. you are walking normally with the left stick and want to aim, the right stick is placed on the left when aiming.

Easyrun lets you run forward automatically if you either press more than 95% LY forward or press L3/LS, or aim twice fast. every time you press a direction or press the crouch button longer and fire, it ends easyrun.

Cam Angle, lets you automatically move the right stick to the left and right with individually set deadzone and strength when you move the left stick, so that you don't have to keep adjusting the camera everytime.

L2 Activ/ R2 Activ , lets you select an invidual button under the controller menu that is activated when an adjustable sensitivity of the trigger button is pressed. for example, L2 activates the shoot button or ping when 95% of the button is pressed, or deadeye as in Readdead redemption.

Dpad to, changes the Dpad to the left or right stick.

Autorun Loot, spam the Loot button (adjustable under Conttroller) while running.

Autorun Parkour, spams the jump button when running (adjustable under Conttroller)

VM Speed speeds up the actions of the zen, for example, the movement of the aim assist is accelerated and is almost no longer visible.

Cancel PolarAngle from Crescens, cancels reload when aiming or firing

Autoreload after fire

Double jump, you can setup in millisecond, when hold the jump button it will press again. example hold jump button and it will press again the jump button after the selected time.

R2 and L2 mod, can set it up under Controller as 

R2 &amp; L2 mods can be selected as a button under the controller menu item when the button is pressed after a preset button. 

Gyro only works with a gyro controller, like the PS4 controller. 

 - Press a button set under Controller in the menu item ACCX Left or right respective button when the controller is tilted. 

 - Turbo will automatically press this button repeatedly as long as the controller is tilted.

 - Race and drift, turns the controller into a steering wheel, for fast movements the drift button can be selected under controller Accx left and right.

 - side walk, lets you walk left and right, under ACCX left and right a button can be selected to make a roll in some games.
 
 Polar V2 is a very smooth aim from Dogz
 
Quick mode can be selected between FPS, Third Party and Recoil on the fly by pressing L2/LT + PS button/Xbox button.

Recoil on the fly, works via L2/LT + Dpad for standard and rumble.

—————————————————————————————————————————————————————————————

Menu item Controller, all buttons are used as in the game.
—————————————————————————————————————————————————————————————

Bumper combo lets you press L1+R1 simultaneously when you briefly press an individually set button. 

Hold BTN lets you keep a button pressed if you press it briefly, a second quick press switches the button off again.

DB Tap LY and LX lets you press a button individually when you press a direction twice. e.g. the B button is on the left and right, so you can quickly move to one side. THX FADEXZ♥

Invert, inverts the right stick

—————————————————————————————————————————————————————————————

Menu item Profile/Remap, triangle/Y changes the mods below.
—————————————————————————————————————————————————————————————
DB Tap, lets you select two individual buttons. pressing one twice activates the other. THX FADEXZ♥

Remap, lets you select two individual buttons to be swapped.
If you select L2 -&gt; R2,( R2 -&gt; L2 is automatically activated.)
—————————————————————————————————————————————————————————————
i hope you like the script and you can play all the games you want.
—————————————————————————————————————————————————————————————</DES><RTP>3</RTP><RTM>4</RTM><UTM>1661766973</UTM><DOW>380</DOW><NOT>2.56
 - Save system
 - added double tap to easyrun and Run and fire(Db tap up the stick and its stop running at fire and continiue running after fire.</NOT><VER>2.56</VER><UNM>SehatHabib</UNM><TID>0</TID></S></GPP>
